## **NASIR TOMLIN**

Phone: 843-214-7753 Email: nasirt@g.clemson.edu

Personal: <a href="mailto:nas.tomlin@gmail.com">nas.tomlin@gmail.com</a>
Portfolio: <a href="mailto:https://nasirtomlin.netlify.app/">https://nasirtomlin.netlify.app/</a>

### **PERSONAL STATEMENT**

Hardworking, reliable, and someone who cooperates well in a team setting. Years of experience with coding, data mapping, and problem-solving. Able to adapt to any environment with a positive impact. An eagerness to learn and willing to grow for improvement.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### Clemson University | Tiger Alliance Program Ambassador

August 2022 - Present

- Planned and implemented program activities for high school students.
- Provided structured educational and recreational opportunities for students.
- Mentor High School students with a path to college.
- Organized and led tours of the campus and various group activities.

### **Clemson University | CONNECTIONS Mentor**

August 2022 - Present

- Mentor first-year students throughout their college experience.
- Host study sessions to improve academic success.
- Meet collectively to create campus activities and host campus events.

## **Clemson University | Undergrads Moving**

May 2021 - Present

- Assisted customers during moves with excellent customer service.
- Work as a team to complete jobs efficiently.
- Showcased great leadership skills to accomplish the end goal.

#### **Lowes | Sales Associate**

May 2021 - Present

- Helping customers find the products they need while providing general assistance.
- Process orders, deliveries, and loaded tickets.
- Forklift Operator.

### A.L.L. SERVICES, LLC | Administrative Assistant

August 2016 - May 2020

- Customer Service.
- Created and faxed invoices.
- Carries out administrative duties such as filing, typing, and copying.

#### **EDUCATION**

# **Clemson University**

August 2020 - Present

# **Bachelor of Science in Computer Science | Minor: Cybersecurity**

- CU Cyber
- Tiger Alliance Ambassador
- CONNECTIONS MENTOR
- Brother2Brother
- Alpha Phi Alpha Fraternity Inc. (2023-2024 Web Design Award, Secretary)

## Skills

- Updating, Designing, and editing website content
- Ethical Hacking
- Leadership Experience
- Microsoft Office 365
- C, C++, Java, SQL, Python
- Database experience
- Management Experience

### **Certifications**

- Microsoft Office
- GIS Pro
- Data Visualization
- Forklift Operator

## **Community Service**

- Helping Hands
- Campus Clean-Up
- Operation Christmas Child
- Lowcountry Food Bank